American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology records
American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology records
Much of the historical information comes from Russell H. Chittenden's work, The First Twenty-Five Years of the American Society of Biological Chemists, published in 1945. Chittenden's history of the early years of the society is an account of the creation and growth of the society and of science in society. Chittenden, as the first President of the society was in a unique position to write the history of the society. There at its creation he was able to watch the society and the fields expand. A special note in the Scope and Content section can be found with more information about this book and its location within the collection. The American Society of Biological Chemists became the American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology in 1987 after the molecular biologists threatened to break away from the Society. ASBMB has continued to grow and currently has over 10,000 members and has created several new journals. The goals of ASBMB are " to advance the science of biochemistry and molecular biology through publication of scientific and educational journals (Journal of Biological Chemistry, Molecular and Cellular Proteomics, Journal of Lipid Research, Biochemistry and Molecular Biology Education), organization of scientific meetings, advocacy for funding of basic research and education, support of science education at all levels, and promoting the diversity of individuals entering the scientific workforce."
Information in this Historical Note was drawn from:
American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology. Accessed February 14, 2008 from http://www.asbmb.org/aboutus.aspx.
Chittenden, Russell H. The First Twenty-Five Years of the American Society of Biological Chemists. 1945.
Organized into five series: Series I. Officers and Executive Council, 1925-2002. Series II. Publications, 1914-2005. Series III. Committees, 1906-2005. Series IV. Meetings, 1906-2002. Series V. Affiliated Organizations, 1933-2002.
Series I. Officers and Executive Council
Presidency
Secretariat
Treasurer
Executive Officer
Association Legal Documents
Miscellaneous ASBM
Series II. Publications
ASBMB News
Editorial Committee
Editorial Board
Publications Committee
Journal of Biological Chemistry
Molecular and Cellular Proteomics
Miscellaneous Publications and Committees
Series III. Committees
Membership Committee
Ad hoc Committees
Armed Forces Committee
Awards Committee
Committee on Biochemical Nomenclature
Committee on Clinical Chemistry
Committee on Equal Opportunities for Minority Groups
Committee on Equal Opportunities for Women
Committee on Human Biochemistry
Committee on Long-Range Goals
Committee on Plans for Scientific Meetings
Committee on Procedures
Committee on Reorganization of Administrative & Business Procedures
Committee on the Professional Training of Biological Chemists
Committee on the Relations of Biochemists to the Reorganization of the Sanitary Corps
Educational Affairs Committee
Feasibility Committee
Future of Biochemistry Committee
Nominating Committee
Past-President's Committee
Public Affairs Committee
Audit Committee
Finance Committee
Committee Appointments and Liaison Officers
Human Relations Subcommittee on Equal Opportunities for Women
Joint Steering for Public Policy Committee (JSPP)
Meetings Committee
Membership Task Force
Series IV. Meetings
Council/Executive Board Meetings
Annual Meetings
Bioterrorism
Finance Meeting
Joint Meetings
Joint Steering for Public Policy Meeting
International Congress of Biochemistry, 1952-1982
Gordon Conference, 1953-1983
Miscellaneous Meetings and Conferences
Series V. Affiliated Organizations
Affiliated Organizations A -B
Affiliated Organizations C
Affiliated Organizations: D-H
Affiliated Organizations: FASEB
Affiliated Organizations: IUB/IUPAC
Affiliated Organizations: I- Keystone
Affiliated Organizations: Government Science Organizations: NAS,NRC, NIH, NLM, NSF
Affiliated Organizations: M-Z
No restrictions.
Finding aid available.
MSS 1996-02; SARCV 2006-03; This collection was donated by the American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology (ABSBMB) under Executive Officer Charles Hancock in March of 1996.
American Society of Biological Chemists; Biochemistry History; Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology; International Union of Biochemistry; Chittenden R. H. (Russell Henry) 1856-1943
American Society for Biochemisty and Molecular Biology (ASBMB). Accessed November 13, 2015.
- Series I. Officers and Executive Council, 1925-2002; 1950-2002 bulk; 27.25 linear feet (27,165 items)
  - Subseries I.A. Presidency, 1950-1991; 57 folders
    - Correspondence, Hubert B. Vickery, 1950-51 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Vincent du Vigneaud, 1951-52 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Henry A. Mattill, 1952-53 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, D. Wright Wilson, 1953-54 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, C. G King, 1954-55 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, J. Murray Luck, 1955-56 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Herbert E. Carter, 1956-57 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, John T. Edsall, 1957-58 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Severo Ochoa, 1958-59 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Harland G. Wood, 1958-60 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Fritz Lipmann, 1959-61 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Esmond E. Snell, 1961-62 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Philip Handler, 1962-63 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Phillip Handler, "Historical Documents and Standing Orders," 1960-66 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, William D. McElroy, 1963-64 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Henry A. Lardy, 1964-65 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Arthur Kornberg, 1965-66 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Stanford Moore, 1966-67 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Konrad E. Bloch, 1967-69 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Bernard L. Horecker, 1968-69 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Paul D. Boyer,1968-70 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Eugene P. Kennedy, 1968-71 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, Christian B. Anfinsen, Jr., 1971-72 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, Albert L. Lehninger, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, Daniel E. Koshland, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, Daniel E. Koshland, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, Daniel E. Koshland, Miscellaneous Materials, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, Irwin C. Gunsalus, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, Irwin C. Gunsalus, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, Peter Berg, 1974-75 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, Peter Berg, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, Robert L. Hill,1976-78 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, Alton Meister,1976-79 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, Mildred Cohn, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Mildred Cohn, 1978-79 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Frederic Richards, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Frederic Richards, 1980-81 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Arthur B. Pardee, 1980-83 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Mary Jane Osborne, 1981-82 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Irwin Fridovich, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Irwin Fridovich, 1982-83 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Earl Stadtman, 1982-84 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Charles Yanofsky, 1984-85 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Edwin Krebs, 1984-86 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Mary Ellen Jones, 1986-87 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Howard Schachman, 1987-88 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Robert Schimke, 1988-90 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, William Lennarz, 1988-90 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, M. Daniel Lane, 1989-91 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Presidency-Correspondence, Robert Wells, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Robert Wells, January- July 2001 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Robert Wells, August- December 2001 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Robert Wells, January- March 2002 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Robert Wells, April-December 2002 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Robert Wells, Animal Rights, 2001- 2002 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Robert Wells, PubMed Central, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Robert Wells, PubMed Central, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Subseries I.B. Secretariat, 1925-1983; 1938-1964 bulk; 21 folders
    - Correspondence, D. W. Wilson, 1925-27 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, H. B. Lewis, 1929-33 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, H. A. Mattill, 1933-35 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Mailings to Members, 1938-46 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, A. K. Balls, "The Case of the Missing Councilor" 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, A. K. Balls, "Post War Problems," 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, O. A. Bessey, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, R. W. Jackson and E. H. Stotz, 1949-52 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, E. H. Stotz, History/Archives, 1950-65 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Phillip Handler, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Phillip Handler, Historian/50th Anniversary Planning, 1955-69 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Frank W. Putnam, Jan-June 1959 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Frank W. Putnam, July-December 1959 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Frank W. Putnam, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Frank W. Putnam, 1961-64 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Thressa C. Stadtman, 1979-81 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, M. J. Coon, 1981- 83 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Ledgers, Receipt and Disbursement Ledger, July 1953-June 1954 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Ledgers, Receipt and Disbursement Ledger, July 1956-June 1957 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Ledgers, Receipt and Disbursement Ledger, July 1959-June 1960 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Ledgers, Receipt and Disbursement Ledger, 1960-62 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Subseries I.C. Treasurer, 1925-1983; 1938-1964 bulk; 72 folders
    - Correspondence, New Treasurer,1946 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1953-56 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1957-59 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, Notes on Treasurer's Duties, 1959-62 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, Waldo E. Cohn, 1959-61 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, Waldo E. Cohn, 1962-65 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, Arthur B. Pardee, 1964-66 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, Arthur Young & Company, 1942-50 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, Arthur Young & Company, 1951-58 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, Arthur Young & Company, 1959-66 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, Arthur Young & Company, 1967-71 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, Arthur Young & Company, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, Arthur Young & Company, 1974-76 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, Arthur Young & Company, 1977-78 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, Arthur Young & Company, 1979-81 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, Arthur Young & Company, 1983-86 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Arthur Young & Company, 1987-91 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Bank of New York, 1987-90 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, The Ealing Corporation, 1974-77 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1915, 1934-36, 1941-49, 1952, 1955-59, 1964-67 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1969, 1977-78 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Dissolution of Assets, 1946-49 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Irving Trust Company, 1928-46, 1958, 1963-68 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Irving Trust Company, 1977-78, 1980-89 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Loomis-Sayles & Company, 1963-71 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Loomis-Sayles & Company, 1972-78 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Maryland National Bank, 1972, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Mercantile Safe Deposit & Trust Company, 1976-78 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Pensions, 1958, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Schwarz/Mann Bioresearch, 1977, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Weiss, Peck & Greer, 1978-79 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Weiss, Peck & Greer, 1980-82 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Weiss, Peck & Greer, 1984-88 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Weiss, Peck & Greer, 1989-91 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Tax/Income Tax Returns, 1933-35, 1941-47, 1951-56 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Tax/Income Tax Returns, 1957-65 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Tax/Public Charities Forms, 1958-62 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Treasurer's- Correspondence, Tax's, 1965, 1967-68 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Reports, 1945-50 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Reports by the Treasurer, 1950-64, 1971, 1976, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Reports, Arthur Young & Company, ASBC Fund, 1942-45, 1953-56 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Reports, Arthur Young & Company, ASBC Fund, 1957-61 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Treasurer Reports, Arthur Young & Company, ASBC Fund, 1962-66 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Reports, Arthur Young & Company, ASBC Fund, 1967-70 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Reports, Arthur Young & Company, ASBC Fund, 1972-79, 1981-82 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - TReports, Arthur Young & Company, Herter Fund, 1942-45, 1953-57 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Reports, Arthur Young & Company, Herter Fund, 1958-62 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Reports, Arthur Young & Company, Herter Fund, 1963-67 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Reports, Arthur Young & Company, Herter Fund, 1968-74 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Reports, Arthur Young & Company, Herter Fund, 1975-79 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Reports, Arthur Young & Company, Herter Fund, 1980-81 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Reports, Arthur Young & Company, Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Reports, Financial Accounts, American Security & Trust Company, 1976, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Reports, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Reports, Irving Trust Company, Statement of Assets, ASBC Fund, 1977, 1983-85, 1987-89 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Reports, Irving Trust Company, Statement of Assets, Herter Fund, 1983-1985, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Reports, Irving Trust Company, ASBC and Herter Funds, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, ASBC Fund, 1959-63 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, ASBC Fund, 1963-65 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, ASBC Fund, 1965-66 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, ASBC Fund, 1966-67 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, ASBC Fund, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, ASBC Fund, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, ASBC Fund, 1977-78 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, Herter Fund, 1959-63 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, Herter Fund, 1963-65 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, Herter Fund, 1965-67 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, Herter Fund, 1968-71 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, ASBC and Herter Funds, 1970-71 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, ASBC and Herter Funds, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, Herter Fund, 1977-78 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, ASBC and Herter Funds, 1982, 1985-88 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Reports, Loomis, Sayles & Company, ASBC and Herter Funds, 1983-85, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Subseries I.D. Executive Officer, 1960-1991; 1964-1991 bulk; 257 folders
    - Personal Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1955-58 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence, Robert Harte, Jan-July 1959 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence, Robert Harte, Aug-Dec 1959 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Personal Correspondence, Robert Harte, Jan-June 1960 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Personal Correspondence, Robert Harte, July-Dec 1960 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Initial, Robert Harte 1960-69 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Personal Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Personal Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Personal Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Personal Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1964-65 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Personal Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1966-67 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Personal Correspondence, & Itineraries, Robert Harte, 1967-71 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Personal Correspondence, & Itineraries, Robert Harte, 1970-71 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Personal Correspondence, ("Critical Reviews"), Robert Harte, 1970-72 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Personal Correspondence, Robert Harte, 1972-77 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Personal Correspondence, Robert Harte, Obituary, Reminiscences, 1977-78 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Personal Correspondence, Miscellaneous, Robert Harte, 1960-68 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Texas A&M University Seminar Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, April-May, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, June-July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, August-Sept 1964 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Oct-Nov 1964 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, December 1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Jan-Feb 1965 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, March 1965 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, April-May, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, June-July 1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, August 1965 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Sept 1965 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, October 1965 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, November 1965 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, December 1965 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, January 1966 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, February 1966 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, March 1966 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, April 1966 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, May 1966 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, June-July 1966 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Aug-Oct 1966 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Nov-Dec 1966 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, January 1967 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, February 1967 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, March 1967 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, April 1967 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, May 1967 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, June-July 1967 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Aug-Sept 1967 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, October 1967 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, November 1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, December 1967 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, January 1968 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Feb-March 1968 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, April 1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, May-June 1968 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, July-Aug 1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Sept-Oct 1968 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, November 1968 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, December 1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, January 1969 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, February 1969 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, May 1969 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, April 1969 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, May 1969 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, June 1969 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, July 1969 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, August 1969 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, September 1969 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Oct-Nov 1969 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, December 1-16, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, December 18-35, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, January 1-25, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, January 26-31, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, February 1-16, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, February 17-27, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, March 1-15, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, March 16-31, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, April 1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, May 1970 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, June 1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, July 1-21, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, July 22-31, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Aug-Sept 1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, October 1-14, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, October 15-31, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, November 1-18, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, November 19-31, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, December 1970 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, January 1971 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Feb-March 1971 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, April-May 1971 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, June-July 1971 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Aug-Sept 1971 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Oct-Nov 1971 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, December 1971 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, January 1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, February 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, March-April 1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, May-June 1972 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, July-Aug 1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Sept-Oct 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Nov-Dec 1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, Jan-Feb 1973 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, March 1973 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Harte, April 1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)